You can get two figures and a drone in one minute.
The first prerequisite is that there must be a drone in the team. Then we choose conventional nuclear power plants,
Come to the middle of the two jars on the right side of the Bioprevention Equipment Research Institute. After entering through this hole,
Come to a room on the right, then take out the drone and put it through the hole.
It should be noted that this drone will break down if it falls into the water. There are a total of five chances.
So if you don’t know how to jump, you can take a look at the anchor’s route.
After coming down, there is a password on the left. Then we go out to the room directly opposite and enter the password.
After entering, there is a password room. The password is fixed, zero-ninety-one.
After entering, go to the small right side, and there is a small room with a small suitcase containing a note.
If you take this note out, you will get another figure. After taking this note,
Carry the drone to the extraction point, and you will finally get two figures and a drone.
It should be noted that the drone strap is a shared note and only counts as personal.